Kinjou seems to have been shy to
talk...
Finally, she gets a
прос seems to be bored
Thank you for watching.
It's starting!
It's starting soon!
It's starting, but it's starting soon.
Can you see it?
It's starting!
Wait a minute.
What should we do?
Did we reach 100 already?
Yes!
Isn't it fast?
Really?
We reached 100 already?
Thank you!
We did it!
Everyone, good evening!
To your heart, rock on!
We are Tokimeki Sentebu!
Thank you!
This week's Tokiwara is a live
broadcast special before the Bicchori
Festival!
So, we have 4 days left until the
Bicchori Festival!
That's right!
That's fast!
We've been doing Spring Tour till
recent though.
Today we can't do the collaboration
sport as well.
So we have to do in Korea anyway.
Thank you!
Thank you.
The new season of the game is just
starting.
And we got the new Shibahira!
It's our first time getting Shibahira.
We were so happy.
We're so thankful that so many people
came to buy the tickets.
Thank you.
Shibahira is still on sale, so if
you're interested, please come and play.
So, this time, Tokibaro is...
What's this?
It's a little A-dex.
So, this time, Tokibaro is...
Let's introduce ourselves.
Let's do it.
I'm Aomoto Ieba.
I'm To Ieba.
I'm Kanamin.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Bambi.
I'm Lemon.
I'm Tokimeki Senzenbu.
I'm To Ieba.
I'm Bambi.
Nice to meet you.
Red of Tokimeki Advertising Club.
To say.
Hitochan, I'm Hitoka Sakai.
I'm 18 years old.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Next, Oharu.
Pink of Tokimeki Advertising Club.
To say.
I'm Haruka Koizumi.
Thank you.
I said thank you.
Next, Julia.
I always forget.
Speaking of Tokimeki Purple...
Speaking of...
Yes, I'm Julia.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Hi! We are Toki Minzy's green and...
I don't remember anything.
I'm Yoshikawa Hiyoi. Thank you for
watching!
Is it Tokimeki White?
Yes, I'm a beautiful white girl.
So, it's Tokimeki White Green.
White Green?
It's a very mild color.
Like a yellow-green.
Yes, so,
this time, Tokibaro is going to
introduce the highlights of Bicchori
Festival 2019.
I think it's a good idea.
I want to start a live stream, but
there's always an opening.
I want to do that from the beginning.
Like a CG that flows with GAMSHALA.
But today is a live stream, so we have
to do it live.
Why?
You can just play it.
It's a live stream, so it's a good
thing.
I don't really understand.
So let's do a narration.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
Ding!
It's a penalty for the White Army
Alright, let's go!
That's it.
Miho, you're not always in the center
of the screen.
I'm always using the one I took before.
Can you say that?
I can.
Really?
You can say that?
I can. I'm relaxed.
You're relaxed?
I'm usually strong.
That's the real thing.
You're relaxed?
I can.
Let's get started.
Let's start the live broadcast of the
festival.
Please click the button.
This program is a program that we, the
6 members who are active to promote
something exciting,
challenge various things and make the
world scream!
And...
I like the way you sing.
I didn't press the button at all.
Is it okay?
Now, let's read the comments.
I want to read it!
Please comment.
It's started.
I like this kind of thing.
We are perfect.
We did our best.
We are finished.
We did it.
Julia has changed a lot.
Please comment what has changed.
What has changed about Julia?
By the way, no one has noticed the
members.
But she is more shiny than usual.
She is shiny.
Julia is shiny.
Really.
She is shiny.
I thought she was shiny.
What is it?
Wait.
Wow.
Her hair is short.
It's been a long time.
It's been a year.
It's amazing.
It's a way to divide.
Did you cut your hair?
I cut it.
I didn't notice it.
I was watching Julia when I was sitting
next to her.
Her hair is more shiny than usual.
Did you cut your hair?
No.
I thought so.
I did it at the hair salon.
It's not like this.
Her genes are different.
I don't like it.
Let's go to the hair salon.
I heard that you are getting a haircut.
Really?
I heard that you are at the hair salon.
What?
Hair salon?
Please come with the hair salon.
I can't wear a hairband.
Can I?
You can.
You are late.
I'm late.
Let's do a 3 minute commercial.
Let's do it.
Let's go to the next.
We will introduce the highlights of the
game.
Let's start with Tsuhina.
This is good.
Where?
Did you hear anything?
It's bad.
Please make it a hate.
There are such words.
This is the last.
The ending that will make FukuBae's
2019 100% happier!
Ta-dah!
What?
Oh!
Ah!
What?
What did you do?
Look!
Yes!
What?
The Lost Throbbing and the Stolen City
of Rain
The theme of this final BITTORI
festival is the Lost Throbbing and the
Stolen City of Rain
The Stolen City of Rain
Sorry
The Lost Throbbing and the Stolen City
of Rain
of Rain is the theme of the game.
The game is about the world after the
Lost Throbbing Festival.
The prologue was released on Twitter.
Did you see it?
The food was dry and the water was
flying.
Fans could call the fans.
They said they were not feeling well.
I think you watched the prologue.
Are you OK?
Some people said they saw it.
Is it?
I think so.
It was more surreal.
It was like a game.
RPG?
A battle?
It was like a grand game.
We played in the desert.
We will take back the beautiful world.
Is that all?
Next is...
Bacchan?
This time...
Next is...
Ta-da!
We're going to perform our new song for
the first time!
We have a new song we're going to
perform for the first time!
Yes!
Um...
This time...
Yes!
Just a little bit!
You want to hear it, right?
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit of the live
broadcast.
Yes.
Um...
It's like this.
What?
Ah, I'm sorry...
It was too weird
I don't know what to do.
What is it like?
This?
How was it?
And...
It's like...
The atmosphere is great.
I like this song a lot.
You know what?
It's really cute.
It's cute.
You should listen to it.
You can't listen to it now.
It depends on whether you can enjoy it
or not.
You should listen to it.
So, everyone.
That's all I can tell you.
Really?
You can tell us more.
Do you want to know more?
It's a song that can make you excited.
It's a refreshing song for summer.
Do you know what I mean?
It's a song that fits summer.
If we talk more, we'll talk a lot.
I'm afraid.
I'm so nervous.
WAMI is...
What's this?
WAMI.
I'm sorry.
It's a song that WAMI likes.
I'm already pushing it.
I'm sorry.
We can't tell you much about it now.
Please come and see it in person.
You can see what WAMI is saying.
Next.
I'll introduce what I'm looking forward
to at the Midori Festival.
Next.
We are the new goods of the 2019
Pitchori Festival.
We are lined up.
Have you seen the commercial of the
goods?
Yes.
I saw it.
I would like to introduce the goods
again from Hitoka today.
What should I introduce first?
Hitoka was doing a commercial.
This is a live photo.
Can I open it?
OK.
I will open it.
I want to do that.
It looks like a YouTube.
Show me one by one.
First, this.
It's Hitoka.
It's a white costume.
It's cute.
Next.
It's already over!
This is fun.
Everyone is feeling this way.
Let's do our best.
Everyone is doing it individually.
It says, this is the number.
Thank you.
Next.
10!
The last one is...
3!
Bye bye!
I didn't get the autograph!
So cute!
Next!
This one!
Ta-da!
Julia!
So cute!
Next!
Bambi!
Bambi's hair is down, so it's super
cute!
Next!
So cute!
Piyo!
Cute!
What's next?
Bye!
Three shots of Kanamin, Julia and Piyo.
Thank you.
Oh my god!
Here it is!
Morning!
The world's autograph!
The world's autograph was in it.
I got it!
So this is what a live photo is like.
It's fun!
I want it!
That's it.
Next!
Next goods.
Yeah, a lot.
Ta-da!
A silicon band.
It's cute!
This is the rumored one!
I'll put it on!
I'll put it on the shelf!
It's analog.
It's not analog.
It's horror.
Kanami!
Listen to this.
The moment I put this on, I, Kanami,
appeared!
What's going on?
I couldn't see you.
I'm scared.
I'm scared in a different way.
Can I take it off?
I can't take it off!
One more time.
Can you move the camera up a little
bit?
Can I take it off?
Don't take it off!
Are you going to take it off?
Let's move on.
I can see it.
I'll put this on and take a picture.
You're a big publicity guy.
I'm a big publicity guy.
Everyone can see it.
Can you see yourself?
Hito-chan!
Hito-chan is cute.
You can see it.
Let's move on.
Next is...
I'll put this on.
This is good.
It's cute.
It's a acrylic key chain.
It's true.
You can put it on the place you want.
You can put it on the key chain.
I gave this to my grandmother.
She decorated it at home.
My grandmother decorated it.
Is it okay?
Let's do it.
Everyone can do it.
Hito-chan, I'll give you a souvenir.
What should I do?
Please subscribe to my channel.
How do I do this?
It's like this.
It's like a real one.
Can I take this?
I want this.
It's like a real one.
I can take this off.
Is this OK?
It's broken.
It's screaming.
I can't open it.
It's not coming out.
I'm going to combine them.
I did it.
It's cute.
Look at this.
What is this?
It's a bandage.
It's really hard.
It doesn't fit.
It's cute.
It's easy.
The back is cute too.
It's like you're at home with your
friends.
I like the back.
Let's put this in front.
Wait, what's going on?
It's like this, right?
The face is coming out.
Really?
The eyes are coming out.
I think it's different.
It's different?
It's definitely different.
It's different.
I want to try this.
The one that says, stop.
I wonder if it'll be fun if we do it
with a kiss.
Please subscribe to our channel.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Don't be surprised.
Can you change the topic?
I'll introduce the next one.
The next one is...
A muffler towel.
This is a classic.
Thank you for watching!
Cute! Look!
It's true!
It's cute!
It's cute.
It's a summer-like pattern.
A belt.
Cute.
It's a different color here.
It says I.C.E. on it.
It's cute.
Next is...
I.C.E.
What are you doing?
Bambi.
I'm done.
Something's different.
But...
What's this?
Something's different.
Flamingo?
It's pink.
There's a flamingo.
No, no, no.
Look closely.
The fruit is different.
It's true!
There's something going on here.
Look!
A strawberry.
I want to eat it.
Strawberry.
It's a strawberry.
It's cute.
It's a melon.
Melon!
Hitoka is really good at this.
And...
Next.
Next, I'll introduce this.
T-shirts.
I'll start with Kanamin.
Mulu.
It's cute.
It's really cute.
It's too cute.
What's this design?
It's really cute.
And...
I talked to my family.
I heard this is similar to Kanamin.
Really?
It's similar to Kanamin.
But the features are really similar.
The eyes are similar.
I want to wear this, but I can't wear
black.
It's cute.
It's a bun.
Bun.
It's cute.
It's similar to Bun.
It's beautiful.
There are a lot of things on her hair.
That's right.
It's a slipper.
It's different.
It's got a slipper.
Fish.
It's cute.
There's a fish.
There?
It's cute.
The eyes are really...
What?
Let's hold our own.
It's really cute.
It's really beautiful.
It's really spring.
It's cute, right?
It's cute.
Can I wear this?
Can I wear it now?
Can I wear it?
Let's wear it now, everyone.
OK.
Wear it from the top.
It's coming from the top.
Yeah.
Mine is big.
Kawaii!
I'm already...
This person is too perfect.
Everyone, please come to the festival
like this.
Like this.
Why are you doing this?
I'm doing this.
It's not a meeting.
I'm doing something.
I'm not flirting.
You're amazing.
Why didn't you give me a towel?
I'm sorry.
Don't flirt.
But if you wear a towel like this, you
can wear a T-shirt even if you get wet.
You can wear a T-shirt with this towel.
If you start the live, you'll get wet,
right?
Then you can buy this again.
But you can wear this and challenge the
live.
You can wear this and challenge the
And I'll buy this when the live is
over.
So buy all red.
Buy one red.
Only red?
Please.
Yuchika, you can buy green.
Can't you put it on?
Let's go to the next one.
Well, anyway...
I'm going to cry.
There are a lot of cute goods, so
please get them.
Let's go on.
Ta-da!
Hikikomori's Hikikomori Map in Tobu
Zoo!
Why are we being shown on the map?
Is it because of the effect?
The other day, Kanamin and Hiyori went
to Tobu Zoo.
We made this Hikikomori map!
Yay!
So, we'd like to briefly introduce the
things that left an impression on us.
Please introduce them to us.
This!
Kawasemi!
First of all, Kawasemi!
It's a roller coaster.
I want to ride it!
Let's ride it!
It was a lot of running.
I don't want to ride it!
It was amazing.
The first one was amazing.
I want to ride it!
I couldn't look forward.
I was scared because I was riding it
first.
I couldn't look forward.
I thought I could do it.
I was looking forward to it.
I want to talk about pancakes.
Pancakes! I saw it.
I ate pancakes!
I ate pancakes with white tiger, fruit,
and chocolate banana.
There was also ice cream.
There was ice cream.
There were 3 kinds of pancakes at the
pancake house in Korone.
I chose the pancake with white tiger.
There are 3 kinds, so please try it.
It's really delicious.
I want you to meet white tiger before
the live.
I want to meet.
It's really cool.
It was a photo NC.
We asked them to take a picture.
But they avoided it.
It was NC.
We can take a picture.
It was over the glass.
It was amazing.
It was close.
I want to go.
Bambi and Julia, do you want to go
together?
Yes.
Before the live.
Let's go together.
Yes.
We have to go before the live.
Let's go.
Let's go to all the places except
Tokyo.
Is it okay?
Yes.
And Alpaca!
Everyone, Alpaca is Haku and Kuu.
It's Haku and Kuu.
Yes.
It's okay.
I don't think they'll do anything.
It was so cute.
I won't do anything.
Right?
I was a little scared.
We said it's scary.
It's scary.
We said it's cute.
We said it's scary.
It's scary.
There are many spots.
If you are interested, please look
around.
If you find something interesting,
please tell us.
Please look at the video.
Please look forward to the next video!
Mia Cat is really cute!
Let's read the comments!
I'll read the comments!
I want to see Mia Cat!
I'm scared of alpacas!
I'm scared of raccoons!
Let's ride the roller coaster!
Do you want to ride it together?
I might leave on the way.
What are you doing?
Are you ready?
I'm really looking forward to it!
You look like Mia Cat.
Thank you.
You look so cute!
Thank you for appearing on the show,
Mia Cat!
I love you, Piyo!
Thank you!
Thank you for appearing on the show,
Mia Cat!
I know!
The strawberry was delicious.
I want to get along with Alpaca.
What was it?
Yoshikawa Cicada.
Yes, Yoshikawa Cicada.
And what was it?
Koizumi.
Yoshikawa Cicada and Koizumi.
What was it?
What?
You said it!
You said it together!
Yoshikawa Cicada and...
That's why I said Yoshikawa Cicada and
Koizumi.
Koizumi?
It's Koi.
Ah, Koi.
You were so calm just now.
I was so calm.
Koi.
It's Koi.
You were so calm when you said fish.
I was so embarrassed.
It's Koi, Yori.
I see.
It's Koi.
Oh, no.
The face is red.
We are not in the best of panda.
We are in the best of panda.
There are also monkey mountains.
Please visit there.
I'm too scared.
I'm not laughing.
Let's go to the next place.
It's dirty around Junior.
It's not good to put garbage around
Junior.
I'm not like that.
Please look forward to the next video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Please check the latest video on
YouTube.
Thank you for your viewing.
Of course, we go to the waterfalls to
splash water.
But this time, we can splash water at
Shibahelia.
What?
I don't want to touch it because it's
shiny.
We can splash water at Shibahelia.
Yes!
It's the final, so it's like a
festival.
Bicchori Festival and Bicchori
Festival, the previous Bicchori Festival
and Bicchori Festival,
It's a new Bicchori Festival that feels
like a combination.
Yes!
It's fun like a combination.
It's so fun that it's fun to be a band.
That's not usually the case...
She said calm down.
I'm not drunk.
Potatoes are popping.
Thank you.
Calm down.
It's like a mix of Bicchuri festival
and Bicchuri festival pre-season.
You're saying something.
For those who have participated before,
it's a reference.
Calm down.
She said calm down.
Let's move on.
The last one is...
It's a little different.
Please subscribe to our channel.
6th, Bicchori Festival is final this
year!
As we announced before, Bicchori
Festival is final this year.
So, let's make the best memories with
everyone who comes to Bicchori Festival!
It says, final answer!
Good!
Final answer!
I can hear you.
What is the final answer?
What?
You two are so mean!
What did you say, Julia?
Do you know what the answer means?
I know.
You said you are better than me.
You are the one who clap with Koizumi.
You two are so mean!
You are so mean!
You look so scary.
It's fine.
Asu-san is fine.
Don't make fun of Asu-san.
Kikui-san, Asu-san is fine.
You are the best!
Thank you!
Ten拿不得啊 Surprisingly I didn't win.
Umeboshi.
Umeboshi!
Let's sing together.
Ready, set, go!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Hitoka!
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
It's white.
It's really white.
I didn't think it would happen.
I was worried.
It's okay.
Thank you!
Happy birthday!
It's tomorrow.
I'll be 18 tomorrow.
17 years old is the last day.
It's the last 17.
The last 17.
Thank you!
I'll go to the bathroom.
I was surprised.
I'm surprised.
Yes, so that's why.
It's not that.
Well, there's such a thing.
Yes, the Bicchori Festival will be the
final.
It's a Bicchori Festival.
Some important new information may be
announced.
If you want to know as soon as
possible, please come to the Bicchori
Festival.
We'll be waiting.
There's only the second one.
Congratulations on the second one.
Everyone is coming.
I'm so happy.
I was worried about what to do with
Kei.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
I'm going to Imanuki on my birthday
tomorrow.
Great.
I'm so happy.
I was happy.
You can stop it.
I'm so sorry.
A press conference.
Please watch it.
I'm 18 years old.
Everyone, please watch it.
Congratulations.
I'll watch it.
I'll watch it in about 4 hours.
It's your birthday?
Yes, it's my birthday.
I'm not going to cry.
I was surprised.
Congratulations.
Let's go to 18 years old.
I'll watch it.
Thank you.
I'll do it early tomorrow.
Iori, calm down.
I'm told to calm down.
Sakai-san.
Yes.
I've been celebrating from the morning.
Sakai-san.
Yes.
This is it.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Hito Calbee.
Hito Calbee is good.
I'll go to bed to wake up tomorrow.
No.
Don't go to bed yet.
Please wait until the live broadcast is
over.
I want to eat this.
I'll go to bed at 2 o'clock.
I'll be sleepy again.
I'll be sleepy again yesterday.
I agree.
I think you should go to bed at 11
o'clock.
11 o'clock.
I think everyone who is watching the
live broadcast will go to bed at 11
o'clock.
Yes.
Thank you for your comments.
Oh, Hiyori, you're in good shape.
Well, as usual.
OK.
Yes, then.
I'd like to start the promotion movie
live special.
Say it again.
I'd like to start the promotion movie
live special.
It's called a screenshot time.
Yes.
Who will go first?
I'll go first.
I'll go last.
The person next to you will hold the
camera.
All right.
You can't screenshot with that.
I'm scared of your face.
What?
Oh, cool.
Everyone.
It's like a screenshot time.
Then Bambi will...
Outside.
What?
I see.
What do you mean?
Everyone...
It says, how do you take a screenshot?
It depends on the article.
It depends on the article, so please
look it up.
Now!
How is it, Kanamin?
Normally, you press the button on both
sides.
Do we do it together?
Yes, yes.
The power button and the volume button.
Bambi!
Kanamin!
For now, please talk!
Everyone, in the comments,
there are people who are teaching us
how to do the screenshot.
Oh, that's nice!
There are people who don't know.
Everyone, please explain to them how to
do the screenshot.
Hey, Kana, solo...
Kana, you're doing this alone, right?
Then, like...
I'll do the screenshot on three
screens.
Oh, let's not do that.
How do you do it?
Is there nothing?
That's a comment.
If you do the screenshot, the power
will go out.
The power will go out.
I got it.
Please keep it in your heart.
Long press the power button.
If you press the power button long, the
power will go out.
The power will go out.
Don't press it long.
It's cute.
You can take a picture with the power
button and volume button.
It's cute.
It's so good.
Don't flirt.
It says, you're too close.
Next.
Hitomi will take Bambi's picture.
Two of us?
Not solo?
Well, we can take a picture.
Can I take a picture of you alone?
I did it.
Bambi's solo version.
Hashtag is alive.
What is it?
Let's take a picture with the power
button.
Let's put in the hashtag.
She said something.
Hashtag is alive.
2019.
Which do you like?
Water?
No.
With or without autograph.
Which do you like?
Hashtag is alive.
Water.
It's a trend.
Hashtag is alive.
That's good.
Thank you.
Hitomi.
Is it good?
Luxury.
We're the same age. Look.
Oh, yeah.
We're still the same age.
We're not the same age yet.
Then I'll be alone at 17.
I'll leave you.
I'll follow you.
I'll follow you after a month.
I'll follow you in less than a month.
I'm honored.
This combination is good.
It's soon.
Hiyori is...
Cute.
Both are cute.
Stop it.
I'm a member.
lol
Thank you!
Hito-chan and Hito-chan's real sound.
Hitoka made it straight iron.
I didn't make it straight iron.
She made it straight iron.
How many degrees should I heat it?
I don't know.
I thought it was 90 degrees because it
didn't make it straight iron.
I didn't make it straight iron.
I'm not straight iron.
It says, Oharu-chan is scary.
Oharu's half eye is gone.
What do you mean?
When you put it on.
Don't put it on.
Remove it where you can't see it.
Your forehead is cute.
What is that?
It says to flirt. Let's flirt.
Julia, run away.
Why do you say that?
That's terrible.
Let's flirt.
No, no, let's do it.
Oharu, Oharu, I love you.
Please react to something.
Julia, I love you.
Yes.
Can you go back to your original
position?
Please go ahead.
Julia, you said you didn't like the
swing.
I don't like it.
456 shot.
She's looking at the screen.
Hi, I love you.
Thank you. I know.
I love you.
Netsuki is 5 times 4.
Wink.
What about a funny face?
Do a funny face.
Cute.
Hina is wearing it.
Don't mind.
5 minutes left.
We will say a word for the last
Bicchori Festival.
There are 4 days left.
Tsujino, please say a word.
I will say.
I think that the contents of today's
live broadcast have been revealed.
I think everyone was looking forward to
it.
How is Bicchori Festival?
There are 4 days left, so please come
and play with high spirits.
We are waiting.
Let's enjoy.
Thank you for the last summer.
We're doing our best. Thank you.
We have 4 days left until the Ritsuri
Festival.
I said it earlier, but the 100 times
more fun part is the highlight.
We have to review that.
We have to sleep early, eat breakfast,
and don't be late for the train.
If we do that, we can buy 2 T-shirts
each.
So we can buy 12 T-shirts.
That's too much.
We can buy 12 T-shirts.
That's all we need.
Let's enjoy the Ritsuri Festival.
They want to see the shrimp-shaped
pose.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I love you.
Bye bye.
You're cute.
I love you.
Kanami.
I'm here.
I'm the leader of the lunch team.
Thank you.
The Ritsuri Festival is full of fun, so
please wear these goods and come to see
us.
We'll be waiting.
You're cute.
See you.
Please watch tomorrow's ImaDoki.
Please watch.
The Ritsuri Festival will be the final
this year. 435 people are watching.
Thank you.
The Ritsuri Festival is the final, so
please enjoy it without any regrets.
We have four days left, so please enjoy
it.
Four days left, and after four days, we
will have the final of the Bichirin
Festival.
It's the last for Julia, but please
enjoy it and don't forget to prepare for
the last four days.
We are waiting for you. Bye-bye.
Let's enjoy the last.
Julia, you are fully prepared.
The Bicchuri Festival will be held in 4
days.
Are you ready?
Please look forward to it.
I'm fully prepared.
I'm scared.
I don't know myself.
Anyway, please look forward to it.
A-Nation.
Yes, the day before yesterday was
In Mie Prefecture.
We will be on the show.
Who?
I'm very nervous.
But the next day is Bicchuri Festival.
I'm really looking forward to it.
So, the Bicchuri Festival in Mie
Prefecture.
The A-Nation Festival in Mie
The Bicchuri Festival in Saitama
Prefecture.
We will do our best.
Please come.
We are waiting for you.
Juri, you are fully prepared.
Why are you suddenly talking about one
thing?
It's a festival.
I'm serious.
If you do that, it will be one minute.
Sorry.
Hiyorin's time is long.
I'm sorry.
Use the rest of the time.
Let's have a screen shot of everyone.
Here we go.
You're holding it?
Let's gather.
Ready, go!
I'll count 10 seconds.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 5, 4, 3, 7, 6
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, everyone, please look forward to
the VTOL.
Please come!
We are waiting!
Bye bye!